const cards = [
  {
    id: 1,
    front: "Hello",
    back: "Bonjour",
    language: "fr-FR",
    translation: "French",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: "Thank you",
    back: "Merci",
    language: "fr-FR",
    translation: "French",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    front: "Goodbye",
    back: "Au revoir",
    language: "fr-FR",
    translation: "French",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    front: "Please",
    back: "S'il vous plaît",
    language: "fr-FR",
    translation: "French",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    front: "Yes",
    back: "Oui",
    language: "fr-FR",
    translation: "French",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    front: "No",
    back: "Non",
    language: "fr-FR",
    translation: "French",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    front: "Good morning",
    back: "Bonjour",
    language: "fr-FR",
    translation: "French",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    front: "Good night",
    back: "Bonne nuit",
    language: "fr-FR",
    translation: "French",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    front: "How are you?",
    back: "Comment ça va?",
    language: "fr-FR",
    translation: "French",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    front: "See you soon",
    back: "À bientôt",
    language: "fr-FR",
    translation: "French",
  },
];

export default cards;
